Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Collection, Part II: Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Non-digitized Tapes, 1956-2001
  - II:B Public Recordings
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Montevideo, Uruguay - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 15, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1011C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in La Paz, Bolivia - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 18, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1012C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in La Paz, Bolivia - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:20:00), Apr 18, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1013C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santa Cruz, Bolivia. (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 19, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1014C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santa Cruz, Bolivia. (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 19, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1015C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cochabamba, Bolivia - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 21, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1016C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cochabamba, Bolivia - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 21, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1017C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in La Paz, Bolivia. (Length: 01:00:00), Apr 22, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1018C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Guayaquil, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 25, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1019C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Guayaquil, Ecuador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 26, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1020C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Guayaquil, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 26, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1021C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cuenco, Equador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 29, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1022C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Cuenco, Equador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 29, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1023C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), May 1, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1024C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), May 1, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1025C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), May 2, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1029C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Quito, Ecuador - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), May 2, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1030C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Casa Grande Reception, Managua, Nicaragua - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), May 4, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1031C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Casa Grande Reception, Managua, Nicaragua - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), May 4, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1032C)
    - Reavy Concert Tape 1. Concert performance by Joe Reavy featuring poetry and songs from Mary Touque, Mike McKinley, Dennis Heron, Dennis Boone, Roy Rogers and music composed by Ed and Joe Reavy. (Length: 01:00:00), May 4, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1034C)
    - Reavy Concert Tape 2. Concert performance by Joe Reavy featuring poetry and songs from Mary Touque, Mike McKinley, Dennis Heron, Dennis Boone, Roy Rogers and music composed by Ed and Joe Reavy. (Length: 01:00:00), May 4, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1035C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), May 11, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1027C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), May 10, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1026C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo Domingo, Dom. Rep., Tape 2. (Length: 00:45:00), May 11, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1028C)
    - Ennis Concert. Second half of a concert performance in Ennis, Co. Clare featuring the Ormond Ceili Band led by Paddy O'Brien (accordion), Mary McNamara (concertina), Jim Curry, Paddy Murphy (concertina), Peadar O'Loughlin (fiddle). (Length: 01:30:00), Jul, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1036C)
    - Miltown Malbay. Fragments of concert performances in Co. Clare. (Length: 00:20:00), Jul, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1037C)
    - Sessions in Miltown. Sessions in Co. Clare with Jimmy Keane (accordion), Moloney (banjo). (Length: 00:45:00), Jul, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1038C)
    - "Irish Fair, Set 1." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 00:45:00), 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm208C)
    - "Irish Fair, Set 2." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 00:45:00), 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1209C)
    - "Irish Fair, Sunday - 1st Set - 3 of 4, 4 of 4." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 01:30:00), 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1210C)
    - "Irish Fair, Last Set, Last Songs, Sun." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in California during the summer. (Length: 00:10:00), 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1211C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance in the Barn at University of California, Riverside. (Length: 01:00:00), Jan, 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1040C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance in Pittsburgh, PA. (Length: 00:30:00), Feb 20, 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1041C)
    - Mick Moloney and Friends. St. Patrick's Day concert performance at Gaston Hall, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Regan Wick (dance). (Length:01:00:00), Mar 17, 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1042C)
    - Session at Moloney's. Quiet session with Mairtin O'Connor (accordion), Dolores Keane (whistle), John Faulkner (mandolin, bouzouki), unidentified flute in Philadelphia, PA., with dog. (Length: 00:50:00), May 19, 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1043C)
    - Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Egan, Siobhan (fiddle) Interview with Earle Hitchener on WFDU, Fairleigh Dickinson University, Madison, NJ. Sibling musicians promote the album, Seamus Egan. Broadcast Jul 12, 1986. (Length: 00:20:00), Jun 14, 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1044C)
    - Central Hotel, Miltown. Session in Co. Clare labeled "Copy S. Egan." (Length: 01:30:00), Jul, 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1236C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, mandolin), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at the Painted Bride Arts Center, Philadelphia, PA. (Length:00:40:00), Oct 21, 1986 (Box 26, Item aiamm1045C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, mandolin), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 0:50:00), Mar 14, 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1046C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, mandolin), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 01:30:00), Mar, 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1047C)
    - "Moloney, O'Connell, Keane - Minneapolis." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], May 29, 1987 (Box 27, Item aiamm1048C)
    - International Village Fair: Celtic and Andean Flutes. Flute workshop in Philadelphia, PA, moderated by Tim Britton comparing Celtic and Andean flutes and flute-playing. (Length: 00:45:00), Jul 26, 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1049C)
    - International Village Fair: O’Donnell & McCafferty Workshop. Workshop performances in Philadelphia, PA. Side A: Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) introduces duets featuring himself and James McCafferty (piano) (15 minutes) followed by Swedish music; Side B: O'Donnell and McCafferty duets (30 minutes) followed by Old-time music. (Total length: 00:45:00), Jul 27, 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1050C)
    - International Village Fair: Workshop performances in Philadelphia, PA. Side A: Afternoon Cape Breton workshop with Maybelle Chisolm McQueen, Buddy MacMaster, David MacIsaacs, John Pellerin; Side B: Wind workshop with Semus Egan (flute)and Tim Britton (uilleann pipes) (Length: 01:30:00), Jul 28. 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1051C)
    - Green Fields of America. Concert performance at UC Santa Barbara, CA. Musicians include: Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Jimmy Keane (accordion). (Length: 00:20:00), Oct 20, 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1052C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, James (accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Concert performance at "Morley's." (Length: 01:20:00), Nov 23, 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1053C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Interview in Los Angeles for Folk Scene, a Pacifica radio show hosted by Howard Larman. (Length: 01:00:00), circa 1987 (Box 26, Item aiamm1054C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Ivers, Eileen (fiddle) Concert performance at the Somerville Theater, Somerville, MA. (Length: 00:20:00), Jan 29, 1988 (Box 26, Item aiamm1055C)
    - Connolly, Seamus (fiddle), Keane, James (accordion), Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo). Concert performance in Convent Station, NJ. (Part one) (Length: 01:00:00), Feb 13, 1988 (Box 26, Item aiamm1056C)
    - Connolly, Seamus (fiddle), Keane, James (accordion), Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo). Concert performance in Convent Station, NJ. (Part two) (Length: 01:10:00), Feb 13, 1988 (Box 26, Item aiamm1057C)
    - Fresh Air. Brief interview and performance by Moloney on the Philadelphia radio show hosted by Terri Gross. (Length: 00:05:00), Feb 19, 1988 (Box 26, Item aiamm1058C)
    - Train to Sligo (group) Concert performance of the California band featuring songwriter Thom Moore, opening for the Grateful Dead. Not Moloney's recording. (Length: 01:00:00), Mar 17, 1988 (Box 26, Item aiamm1059C)
    - Newsmark Magazine, "Irish in America." CBS News radio broadcast featuring Moloney discussing contemporary Irish immigration and the Irish in America. (Length: 00:15:00), Jul 15, 1988 (Box 26, Item aiamm1060C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) Concert performance at the Old Songs Festival, Altamont, NY. (Length:00:35:00), circa 1989 (Box 26, Item aiamm1061C)
    - Concerts in Alaska. Side A: Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Dirk Powell (piano) Concert performance at the fifteenth annual Alaska Folk Festival, Juneau; Side B: Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connoll (guitar, vocals) Concert performance at Grand Central Station, Anchorage. (Total length: 01:15:00), Apr 1989 and Jan 6, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1062C)
    - Augusta Irish Week. Concert performance at the seventh year of the event in Elkins, WV. Musicians include: Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Donna Long (piano), Carol Thompson (harp), Frank Harte (vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Jack Coen (flute), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Myron Bretholtz (bodhran), Natalie MacMaster (fiddle), Beaton, MacIsaac. (Length: 00:45:00), Jul 25, 1989 (Box 26, Item aiamm1063C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at Grand Central Station, Anchorage, AL. (Length:01:20:00), Jan 6, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1064C)
    - Celtic Traditions, WFDU, Fairleigh Dickinson University, Madison, NJ. Three phone interviews by host Danny Quinn followed by musical excerpts. Side A) Mick Moloney and Seamus Egan. Side B) Paddy Moloney. Each discuss their personal and musical histories. (Length: 01:30:00), Feb 23, 1991, Oct 29, 1990, and Dec 1, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1065C)
    - WUGA Centerlines - Mick Moloney phone Interview on Georgia radio about Moloney, O'Connell and Keane concert in Athens, GA. (Length: 00:15:00), Apr 6, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1213C)
    - Connolly, Seamus (fiddle), Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo) Interview and performance on the Over Home radio show, Mountain Heritage Center, Western Carolina University, Cullowhee, NC. (Length: 01:00:00), Jun 17, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1066C)
    - Augusta Irish Week. Lunch time concert performance in Elkins, WV. featuring new composition and songs. Musicians: Mick Moloney (vocals), Frank Harte (vocals), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Jack Coen (flute), Bob McQuillan (piano), Seamus Egan (flute), Joanie Madden (flute) (Length: 00:45:00), Jul 24, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1067C)
    - Augusta Irish Week. Lunch time concert performance in Elkins, WV. featuring songs. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals), Frank Harte (vocals), Joe and Siobhan O'Donovan and a storyteller named Eddie. (Length: 00:40:00), Jul 26, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1068C)
    - "Augusta - Moloney, Egan, O'Donnell, McLeod." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Jul, 1990 (Box 27, Item aiamm1069C)
    - "Selections from Augusta Irish Week (Mostly)." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Jul, 1990 (Box 27, Item aiamm1070C)
    - Long Note. Irish radio program hosted by Maire O'Keefe featuring John Williams (concertina) discussing his life, music and Chicago. (Length: 00:30:00), Nov 15, 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1071C)
    - Old Traditions, New Sounds. "Martin Mulhaire," Episode four of a thirteen part radio series profiling ethnic musicians (produced by Becky Miller for the World Music Institute) features the Galway accordionist. (Length: 00:30:00), circa 1990 (Box 26, Item aiamm1072C)
    - Augusta Scottish Week. Ceili with "Buddy and Dougie" (fiddle and piano) and singers. (Length: 01:30:00), 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1074C)
    - "Women in Irish Music: Music for Mick’s Lecture." Excerpts from commercial recordings and broadcast interviews of members of Dublin Irish women ensemble, Macalla, including Nollaig Casey and Mary Bergin. Interviews are not by Moloney. (Length: 00:20:00), 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1075C)
    - St. Patrick's Day. Concert performance in Philadelphia PA. Musicians: Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Michael Aharon (piano), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Natalie MacMaster (fiddle), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar), Cherish the Ladies featuring Joanie Madden (flute), Mary Coogan (guitar), Cathie Ryan (vocals), Maureen Doherty (flute), Siobhan Egan (fiddle), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Bridget Fitzgerald (vocals). (Length: 01:00:00), Mar 17, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1076C)
    - "International House - St. Patrick’s Day." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Mar 17, 1991 (Box 27, Item aiamm1077C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), MacMaster, Natalie (fiddle), Wick, Regan (dance) Concert performance in Rosemont, Chicago, IL. (Length: 01:30:00), Mar, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1078C)
    - Healy, Shay (vocals, guitar) Concert performance at noisy Mulligan's Bar, Nashville, TN. (Length 01:40:00), May 24, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1079C)
    - Augusta Irish Week: "Tuesday Concert." Concert performance in Elkins, WV during the event's tenth year. Musicians include: Carol Thompson (harp), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Jack Coen (flute), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Myron Bretholtz (bodhran), Kevin Burke (fiddle), Johnny Moynihan (vocals), Mattie Connolly (uilleann pipes), Winifred Horan (dance) (Part one) (Length: 01:20:00), Jul 23, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1080C)
    - Augusta Irish Week: "Tuesday Concert." Concert performance in Elkins, WV during the event's tenth year. Musicians include: Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Donna Long (piano), Joanie Madden (flute), Zan McLeod (bouzouki), Donnie Golden (dance), Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo) (Part two) (Length: 01:00:00), Jul 23, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1081C)
    - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, banjo), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) Concert performance at the Cuyahoga Valley Festival, OH. (Length: 00:25:00), Aug 24, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1082C)
    - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, banjo), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) Concert performance at the Cuyahoga Valley Festival, OH. (Length: 00:45:00), Aug 25, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1083C)
    - Augusta Irish Week: "Dance." Hissy lunch concert dance demonstration with Donny Golden (dance), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle). (Length: 00:45:00), Aug, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1084C)
    - "WXPN Show: Self and 78s / McGinty's etc." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Sep 22, 1991 (Box 27, Item aiamm1085C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance in Ottowa, CAN. (Length: 01:30:00), Oct 1, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1086C)
    - Green Fields of America and Cherish the Ladies. Concert performance. Musicians include Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Cherish the Ladies. (Length: 01:00:00), Dec 23, 1991 (Box 26, Item aiamm1087C)
    - "Tour of ‘92." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], 1992 (Box 27, Item aiamm1088C)
    - " Next Market Day #3." Radio program on WGDR, Plainfield, NJ, hosted by Maureen Harkin featuring Irish music and songs.(Length: 00:15:00), Mar 17, 1992 (Box 26, Item aiamm1089C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar) Interview for Music of the Isle community radio show in Tampa, FL. Moloney discusses Celtic music. (Length: 00:20:00), Apr, 1992 (Box 26, Item aiamm1090C)
    - Byrne, James (fiddle), Moloney, Mick (guitar, banjo) Intimate concert performance with Donegal fiddler, Byrne featuring Moloney discussing music. (Length: 01:30:00), Sep 30, 1992 (Box 26, Item aiamm1091C)
    - Moloney, Mick (guitar, banjo, vocals), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Connolly, Seamus (fiddle) Concert performance in Fairbanks, AK. (Part one) (Length:01:30:00), Oct 25, 1992 (Box 26, Item aiamm1092C)
    - Moloney, Mick (guitar, banjo, vocals), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Connolly, Seamus (fiddle) Concert performance in Fairbanks, AK. (Part two) (Length:00:30:00), Oct 25, 1992 (Box 26, Item aiamm1093C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance at the Barn, UC Riverside, Los Angeles, CA. (Length: 00:45:00), 1993 (Box 26, Item aiamm1094C)
    - Williams, John (accordion) Hayes, Martin (fiddle) Concert performances at the University of Chicago Folk Festival. Not recorded by Moloney. (Length 01:00:00), Feb 12-Feb 13, 1993 (Box 26, Item aiamm1095C)
    - Folk Masters Radio broadcast hosted by Nick Spitzer featuring concert performance and interviews with Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), James Keane (accordion). (Length: 00:35:00), Mar 19, 1993 (Box 26, Item aiamm1096C)
    - Augusta Irish Week. Final set of an evening concert performance in Elkins, WV. Musicians include: Billy McComiskey (accordion), Zan McLeod (bouzouki), James Kelly (fiddle), Winifred Horan (dance), Donnie Golden (dance), Larry Lynch, Albert Alfonso (bodhran), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina) (Length: 00:20:00), Jul 27, 1993 (Box 26, Item aiamm1097C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) End of a concert performance followed by Colum and Ben Sands with Colum McEvoy (painter) and the Fiddle Puppet Dancers at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Lenfgth: 00:45:00), Mar 14, 1994 (Box 26, Item aiamm1098C)
    - Celtic Appalachia #1. Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Jimmy Crowley (bouzouki, vocals). (Length: 01:30:00), Mar 15, 1994 (Box 26, Item aiamm1099C)
    - "Irish Music Song and Dance: 2 of 2." End of afternoon World Music Institute Concert at Symphony Space, NYC. Musicians include:Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Donnie Golden (dance), Cathie Ryan (vocals), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Joanie Madden (flute) and unidentified conga drummer. Golden teaches a ceili dance. (Length: 00:10:00), Apr 16, 1994 (Box 26, Item aiamm1100C)
    - Augusta Irish Week. First half of evening concert performance in Elkins, WV. during the event's thirteenth year. Musicians include: Carol Thompson (harp), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Frank Harte (vocals), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Eileen Ivers (fiddle). (Length: 01:00:00), Jul 26, 1994 (Box 26, Item aiamm1101C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. preceded by the Fiddle Puppet Dance troupe. (Length: 00:45:00), circa 1994 (Box 26, Item aiamm1102C)
    - Celtic Appalachia #2. Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Mac Benford (old time banjo), Tommy Sands (guitar, vocals), Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Lisa Gutkin (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes). (Length: 00:45:00), Mar 15, 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1103C)
    - Willie Clancy Festival. Poor quality recording of flute and whistle concert in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare. (Length: 00:55:00), Jul 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1104C)
    - "Session on Tour." Session with Moloney, accordion, guitar and lots of background noise at Dan O'Connell's, Knocknagree, Co. Cork. (Length: 01:30:00), Aug 4, 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1105C)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival. Moloney lecture entitled "Traditional Irish Music in America." (Length: 00:45:00), Aug, 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1106C)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival. Tuesday Moloney lecture entitled "Irish Dance Bands in America." (Length: 01:00:00), Aug, 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1107C)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival. Moloney lecture entitled "Women in Irish Music" cont'd. and Thursday lecture entitled "Irish Music Today." (Length: 01:00:00), Aug, 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1108C)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival. Wednesday Moloney lecture entitled "Women in Irish Music." (Length: 01:00:00), Aug, 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1109C)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival. Moloney lecture entitled "Songs of the Famine." (Length: 01:00:00), Aug, 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1110C)
    - "Milwaukee Inflight Program Material." Promotional material for the Milwaukee Irish Festival featuring Liz Carroll (fiddle), Joanie Madden (flute), Harry Bradshaw, Ron Kavanaugh. Many short spots from fifteen seconds to a minute in length. (Length: 00:45:00), circa 1995 (Box 26, Item aiamm1111C)
    - Mollys (group) Concert performance at an Irish festival featuring bass, drums and accordion. (Length: 00:20:00), 1996 (Box 26, Item aiamm1112C)
    - Peace Concert. (Part one of two) Concert performance at Symphony Space in New York, NY. Musicians: Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Tommy Sands (vocals, guitar), Vedran Smailovic (cello). (Length: 01:30:00), Mar 1, 1996 (Box 26, Item aiamm1113C)